export const QuizDataJava = [
    {
        question: "What is Java?",
        options: ["A front-end JavaScript library", "A back-end JavaScript runtime environment", "A high-level, class-based, object-oriented programming language", "A version of jQuery"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which company developed Java?",
        options: ["Microsoft", "Sun Microsystems", "Apple", "IBM"],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a core component in Java?",
        options: ["JDK", "JRE", "JVM", "All of the above"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What does JVM stand for?",
        options: ["Java Virtual Machine", "Java Variable Method", "Java Vector Machine", "None of the above"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of 'public static void main(String[] args)' in Java?",
        options: ["It's the entry point for any Java program", "It's a method to print output", "It's a method to take input", "None of the above"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of 'System.out.println' in Java?",
        options: ["To import modules", "To export modules", "To print output to the console", "None of the above"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which method is used to read a file in Java?",
        options: ["FileReader", "FileWriter", "BufferedReader", "BufferedWriter"],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following is a built-in Java command?",
        options: ["System.exit(0)", "System.out.println", "System.in.read", "All the above"],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: "What is the purpose of 'this' keyword in Java?",
        options: ["To refer to the current object", "To refer to the parent class", "To refer to the child class", "None of the above"],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: "What does 'Object-oriented' mean in Java?",
        options: ["Code is executed line by line", "Code is based on real-world objects", "Code is executed based on user actions", "None of the above"],
        answer: 2
    },
];